<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>containers on Plex Engineering</title><link>https://plexsystems.github.io/categories/containers/</link><description>Recent content in containers on Plex Engineering</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://plexsystems.github.io/categories/containers/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Introducing Sinker: A tool to sync container images from one registry to another</title><link>https://plexsystems.github.io/posts/introducing-sinker/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Jul 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://plexsystems.github.io/posts/introducing-sinker/</guid><description>At Plex, all container images in our environments are sourced from our internal container registries. While this gives us greater control over which images can and cannot be used in our environments, it poses a bigger problem. How can we leverage container images that are managed in the public cloud?
A common solution to this problem is to sync the public container image to your organization&amp;rsquo;s private registry by pulling down the image and then pushing it to your internal registry.</description></item><item><title>Testing Containers with Container Structure Test</title><link>https://plexsystems.github.io/posts/container-structure-test/</link><pubDate>Mon, 08 Jun 2020 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://plexsystems.github.io/posts/container-structure-test/</guid><description>It is no secret that when we are writing software, tests are a critical component to ensure the code actually does what we say it does. It is so critical that most languages come with testing frameworks. JavaScript has testing frameworks such as mocha and jasmine. Go ships with its own testing capabilities provided by the testing package. And while writing tests in these languages is an accepted standard practice, all too often we forget that there is more to getting an application onto production than the app itself.</description></item></channel></rss>